profsurv.com 2011-05-25

# Privacy Policy: Professional Surveyor Magazine

Flatdog Media, Inc. knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting profsurv.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

### What Personal Information about Customers Does Flatdog Media, Inc. Gather?

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at profsurv.com. Here are the types of information we gather.

  * Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. Scroll to the bottom of this page to see examples of what we collect. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you. 
  * Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses profsurv.com. We do not store personal information or credit card numbers as a cookie on your computer. Scroll to the bottom of this page to see examples of the information we receive. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at profsurv.com if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist. 

### What about Cookies?

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. 
  * We do not store personal information or credit card numbers as a cookie on your computer and do not plan to do so in the future. 
  * The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of profsurv.com's coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

### How Secure Is Information about Me?

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.

  * We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. 
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit profsurv.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Maryland. If you have any concern about privacy at profsurv.com, please send us a thorough description to feedback@ProfSurv.com, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes, Related Practices and Information

### Conditions of Use

Automatic Information:  Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; e-mail address; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; and cookie number.
